less than 10 percentage from 200 dma so
[Music]
um
which is which we are getting from
[Music]
which you are getting from
me
okay
penetration
insurance penetration require insurance
insurance penetration
3.2 percentage of rasmussen career so in
2001 life insurance penetration goes to
three point two in the year to the
corona virus did what no amount of
advertisement to life is couldn't do it
pushed alive from india so two point
eight two three point two zero
foreign
[Music]
so it's one of the leading and
established private general insurance
company in india so india
um
[Music]
foreign
ninety three quarter four thousand seven
seven crores so the super duper it means
it is a second highest
sales series
which is almost equal
[Music]
uh
so
um
[Music]